brilliantstore.com 2007-12-03

# Brilliantstore.com Privacy Policy

Service Desk

How to Contact

Get answer to your questions within 3 hours or less! 

_**E-mail**_

General Information:

Customer Service Department:

Purchasing Department:

Business development Department:

IT Department:

_**Phone**_

877-383-5641

510-668-0398

(M - F 8:30 AM - 5:30 PM PDT)

_**Fax**_

510-751-5309

_**By Mail**_

Brilliant Store 933 Corporate Way, Fremont, CA 94539

If you want to pick up your order at Brilliant Store, 

to get driving directions.

|  | 

Brilliant Store Service Desk

Brilliant Store Privacy Policy

Brilliant store does not collect personally identifiable information from individuals unless they provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. This means we don't require visitors to register or provide information to us in order to view our site. Whether we gather your personal or corporate information on the Internet, or by other means, we pledge:

  * We ship your order with plain packages, no indication of contents will be shown on the packages;
  * Not to sell, giveaway, or otherwise communicate your personal or corporate information to any other persons or companies;
  * To use your personal information to provide you with information or materials only if you requested;
  * To provide you, the customer, with the opportunity to remove your information from our database, at your request.

Brilliant store does not and will not engage in the following activities:

  * unsolicited email or postal mail,
  * unsolicited phone call or Fax.

We contact you via email only for the following purposes:

  * Order confirmation and delivery notice,
  * Other order-related issues, if any, and
  * Answer to your inquiry

If you have any question or concern about brilliant store's privacy policy, please 

to let us help you.
